Guide to the Communist Party of the United States of America Audio Collection TAM.132.001
Tamiment Library and Robert F. Wagner Labor Archive
- Series IV: Audio Cassette Tapes: Public Events
  - Subseries IV:E: Unidentified
    - Unidentified Conference. Building the Party, People's Daily World and the Young Communist League (Workshop 5). Tape 1 *, undated (Box 55, Cassette 4213)
    - Unidentified Conference. Building the Party, People's Daily World and the Young Communist League (Workshop 5). Tape 2 *, undated (Box 55, Cassette 4212)
    - Unidentified Conference. Building the Party, People's Daily World and the Young Communist League. Tape 1 *, undated (Box 55, Cassette 4215)
    - Unidentified Conference. Building the Party, People's Daily World and the Young Communist League. Tape 2 *, undated (Box 55, Cassette 4214)
    - Unidentified Conference. Includes Gus Hall, Jarvis Tyner, Lee Dlugin, and Timor Timofeyev. Tape 2, undated (Box 55, Cassette 4250)
    - Unidentified Conference. Includes Gus Hall, Lee Dlugin, Henry Winston, and Timor Timofeyev. Tape 1, undated (Box 55, Cassette 4249)
    - Unidentified Conference. Includes Henry Winston and Sam [Webb?]. Tape 3, undated (Box 55, Cassette 4263)
    - Unidentified Conference. Includes Sylvia Newcome and Henry Winston. Tape 2, undated (Box 55, Cassette 4264)
    - Unidentified Conference. James Steele, Summary. Tape 8, undated (Box 55, Cassette 4256)
    - Unidentified Conference. Labor Workshop and Opening Report, William Williamson. Tape 1 *, undated (Box 55, Cassette 4211)
    - Unidentified Conference. Labor Workshop, William Williamson. Tape 2 *, undated (Box 55, Cassette 4210)
    - Unidentified Conference. Report Back from Workshops. Includes Michael Zagarell, George Meyers, James Jackson, Fania Davis, Arnold Becchetti, Louis Weinstock, and Fern Winston. [Tape 1?] *, undated (Box 55, Cassette 4233)
    - Unidentified Conference. Report Back from Workshops. Includes Michael Zagarell, George Meyers, James Jackson, Fania Davis, Arnold Becchetti, Louis Weinstock, and Fern Winston. [Tape 2?], undated (Box 55, Cassette 4234)
    - Unidentified Conference. Session 1, The Theory of Scientific Socialism. Tape 1, undated (Box 52, Cassette 4084)
    - Unidentified Conference. Session 1, The Theory of Scientific Socialism. Tape 2, undated (Box 52, Cassette 4085)
    - Unidentified Conference. Session 2, Discussion of the Capitalist Situation and the Crisis of Neo-Liberalism. Tape 3, undated (Box 52, Cassette 4086)
    - Unidentified Conference. Session 2, Discussion of the Capitalist Situation and the Crisis of Neo-Liberalism. Tape 4, undated (Box 52, Cassette 4087)
    - Unidentified Conference. Session 3, Discussion of the Technological and Scientific Revolutions and their Effects on the Economic and Social Environments. Tape 5, undated (Box 52, Cassette 4088)
    - Unidentified Conference. Session 3, Discussion of the Technological and Scientific Revolutions and their Effects on the Economic and Social Environments. Tape 6, undated (Box 52, Cassette 4089)
    - Unidentified Conference. Session 3, Discussion of the Technological and Scientific Revolutions and their Effects on the Economic and Social Environments. Tape 7, undated (Box 52, Cassette 4090)
    - Unidentified Conference. Session 4, Significance and Consequences of NAFTA. Tape 10, undated (Box 55, Cassette 4093)
    - Unidentified Conference. Session 4, Significance and Consequences of NAFTA. Tape 11, undated (Box 55, Cassette 4094)
    - Unidentified Conference. Session 4, Significance and Consequences of NAFTA. Tape 12, undated (Box 55, Cassette 4094A)
    - Unidentified Conference. Session 4, Significance and Consequences of NAFTA. Tape 8, undated (Box 55, Cassette 4091)
    - Unidentified Conference. Session 4, Significance and Consequences of NAFTA. Tape 9, undated (Box 55, Cassette 4092)
    - Unidentified Conference. Tape 13, undated (Box 55, Cassette 4095)
    - Unidentified Conference. Tape 14, undated (Box 55, Cassette 4096)
    - Unidentified Conference. Tape 15, undated (Box 55, Cassette 4097)
    - Unidentified Conference. Tape 16, undated (Box 55, Cassette 4098)
    - Unidentified Discussion [on Black-White Unity], undated (Box 32, Cassette 4989)
    - Unidentified Discussion [on Student Recruitment]. Tape 3, undated (Box 32, Cassette 4950)
    - Unidentified Discussion of Communist Party, USA Electoral Policy. Tape 4, undated (Box 32, Cassette 4987)
    - Unidentified Discussion of Education Programming. Tape 3, undated (Box 32, Cassette 4885)
    - Unidentified Discussion of Party History, undated (Box 32, Cassette 4986)
    - Unidentified Discussion of the Women's Movement, undated (Box 32, Cassette 4943)
    - Unidentified Discussion on Health Care, undated (Box 32, Cassette 4856)
    - Unidentified Discussion. Includes Gus Hall. Tape 5 (?), undated (Box 32, Cassette 4860)
    - Unidentified Disscussion on the Youth Question, undated (Box 32, Cassette 4932)
    - Unidentified Event. Includes Lewis Moroze (?), undated (Box 32, Cassette 4864)
    - Unidentified Interview on Irving Potash, undated (Box 32, Cassette 4840)
    - Unidentified Interview on the National Caucus of Labor Committees, undated (Box 28, Cassette 1160)
    - Unidentified Interviews on Life in the Democratic People's Republic of Korea, with representatives from the Palestine Liberation Organization and other topics) *, undated (Box 32, Folder 5004)
    - Unidentified Interview with Representative from Iraq Concerning Sanctions and Blockades, undated (Box 32, Cassette 4892)
    - Unidentified Leadership Seminar, undated (Box 32, Cassette 4851)
    - Unidentified Lecture. On Election Campaign, undated (Box 58, Cassette 1277)
    - Undentified Lecture [on Israel], undated (Box 32, Cassette 4984)
    - Unidentified Lecture. On Materialist Philosophy (Topic 2). Tape 3, undated (Box 32, Cassette 4960)
    - Unidentified Lecture. On the Black Jewish National Question, undated (Box 59, Cassette 984)
    - Unidentified Lecture. On the Free Angela Davis Campaign, undated (Box 32, Cassette 4814)
    - Unidentified Lecture. On the Trade Union Movement and Youth / Music, undated (Box 32, Cassette 4880)
    - Unidentified Marxist Symposium. New York, NY. [Tape 1], undated (Box 55, Cassette 4230)
    - Unidentified Marxist Symposium. New York, NY. Tape 2, undated (Box 55, Cassette 4231)
    - Unidentified Meeting, undated (Box 44, Cassette 2638)
    - Unidentified Meeting, undated (Box 40, Cassette 2404)
    - Unidentified Meeting, undated (Box 40, Cassette 2405)
    - Unidentified Meeting, undated (Box 44, Cassette 2594)
    - Unidentified Meeting. [Condition poor: creation of user copy may pose problems. Contact tamiment.wagner@nyu.edu], undated (Box 44, Cassette 2632)
    - Unidentified Meeting, undated (Box 28, Cassette 1278)
    - Unidentified Meeting, undated (Box 32, Cassette 4817)
    - Unidentified Meeting. Bureau of the World Peace Council, undated (Box 44, Cassette 2640)
    - Unidentified Meeting. "Cyril at W.F. N.H.", undated (Box 32, Cassette 4915)
    - Unidentified Meeting. [Communists and Labor Organizing?]. Tape 1, undated (Box 32, Cassette 4810)
    - Unidentified Meeting. [Communists and Labor Organizing?]. Tape 2, undated (Box 32, Cassette 4811)
    - Unidentified Meeting. Discussion on the Youth Question and the Role of the Young Communist League, undated (Box 32, Cassette 4917)
    - Unidentified Meeting. Discussion. Tape 2, undated (Box 32, Cassette 4834)
    - Unidentified Meeting. Discussion. Tape 3, undated (Box 32, Cassette 4835)
    - Unidentified Meeting. Gus Hall, Final Remarks. Tape 6, undated (Box 55, Cassette 4252)
    - Unidentified Meeting. Includes Charlene Mitchel, undated (Box 32, Cassette 4873)
    - Unidentified Meeting. Includes Daniel Rubin, undated (Box 32, Cassette 4975)
    - Unidentified Meeting. Includes Evalutaion of Leadership Seminar, People's Daily World Fundraising Drive, Young Communist League Convention, undated (Box 32, Cassette 4816)
    - Unidentified Meeting. Includes Gus Hall and James Steele. Communication from the Central Committee of the Soviet Union, undated (Box 32, Cassette 4809)
    - Unidentified Meeting. Includes James Jackson, undated (Box 32, Cassette 4914)
    - Unidentified Meeting. Includes Jim and Discussion. Tape 4, undated (Box 32, Cassette 4836)
    - Unidentified Meeting. Includes Jim and Discussion. Tape 5, undated (Box 32, Cassette 4837)
    - Unidentified Meeting. Includes Jim, Bob and Elena [Mora]. Tape 1, undated (Box 32, Cassette 4833)
    - Unidentified Meeting. Includes Jim, Keta and Larry. Tape 6, undated (Box 32, Cassette 4838)
    - Unidentified Meeting. Includes Keta and Discussion. Tape 7(?), undated (Box 32, Cassette 4839)
    - Unidentified Meeting. Includes Saul [Alinsky?], Henry Winston and Daniel Rubin. Tape 5, undated (Box 32, Cassette 4979)
    - Unidentified Meeting. James Steele, Report on Young Communist Leauge Electoral Campaign, undated (Box 32, Cassette 4926)
    - Unidentified Meeting. Marj Southerland, Discussion of Tacoma Protest Meeting on Economic Fightback. Tacoma, WA, undated (Box 32, Cassette 4937)
    - Unidentified Meeting. On Trade Unionism, undated (Box 55, Cassette 4208)
    - Unidentified Meeting. [On Youth and Education?]. Side 2, undated (Box 32, Cassette 4927)
    - Unidentified Meeting. [On Youth and Education?]. Side 3, undated (Box 32, Cassette 4928)
    - Unidentified Meeting. [On Youth and Education?]. Sides 5 and 6, undated (Box 32, Cassette 4929)
    - Unidentified Meeting. [On Youth and Education?]. Sides 7 and 8, undated (Box 32, Cassette 4930)
    - Unidentified Meeting. Tape 1, undated (Box 55, Cassette 4274)
    - Unidentified Meeting. Tape 2, undated (Box 32, Cassette 4807)
    - Unidentified Meeting. Tape 3, undated (Box 55, Cassette 4276)
    - Unidentified Meeting. Tape 3, undated (Box 32, Cassette 4806)
    - Unidentified Meeting. Tape 4, undated (Box 32, Cassette 4805)
    - Unidentified Meeting. Tape 5, undated (Box 55, Cassette 4277)
    - Unidentified Meeting. Tape 5, undated (Box 32, Cassette 4804)
    - Unidentified Meeting. Tape 7, undated (Box 55, Cassette 4279)
    - Unidentified Meeting. Tape 8, undated (Box 55, Cassette 4280)
    - Unidentified Microcassette. [Creation of user copy may pose problems. Contact tamiment.wagner@nyu.edu], undated (Box 32, Cassette 5013)
    - Unidentified National Meeting. [Milwaukee, WI?], undated (Box 32, Cassette 4944)
    - Unidentified [New York Times?] Conference. Pat and John (?), on Racism, undated (Box 58, Cassette 1124)
    - Unidentified Oral History Interview, undated (Box 32, Cassette 4818)
    - Unidentified Panel Discussion. Questions and Answers, undated (Box 32, Cassette 4870)
    - Unidentified Questions and Answers. Includes Erwin Marquet, Victor Perlo and James Jackson, undated (Box 52, Cassette 4043)
    - Unidentified Rally. Includes Gus Hall, Antar Mberi and James [Jackson?], undated (Box 32, Cassette 4956)
    - Unidentified Theatrical Production. Includes David Olson and Becky Armstrong, undated (Box 55, Cassette 4242)
    - Unidentified Tokyo Conference, On Hiroshima, undated (Box 36, Cassette 1074)
    - Unidentified Workshop and Discussion of Elections by Marth Rubin / 50th Wedding Anniversary Celebration for Hyman and Rose Jackie, undated (Box 55, Cassette 4112)
    - Unidentified Youth Conference. Part 2, undated (Box 32, Cassette 4812)
    - Unidentified Youth Meeting, undated (Box 55, Cassette 4166)
    - Unidentified, undated (Box 45, Cassette 1867)
    - Unidentified, undated (Box 45, Cassette 1933)
    - Unidentified, undated (Box 55, Cassette 4283)
    - Unidentified, undated (Box 59, Cassette 1075)
  - Subseries IV:F: Speakers' Lists and Related Materials
    - Speakers' Lists and Related Materials (Box 60)
  - Subseries IV:G: Original Containers
    - Cassettes: Original Containers (empty) [#860-1339] (Box 50, Cassette 860-1339)
    - Cassettes: Orignial Containers (empty) [#1340-1794] (Box 61, Cassette 1340-1794)
    - Cassettes: Original Containers (empty) [#1830-2755] (Box 81, Cassette 1830-2755)
    - Cassettes: Original Containers (empty) [#2756-3077] (Box 80, Cassette 2756-3077)
    - Cassettes: Original Containers (empty) [#3078-3742] (Box 79, Cassette 3078-3742)
    - Cassettes: Original Containers (empty) [#3743-4390] (Box 78, Cassette 3743-4390)
    - Cassettes: Original Containers (empty) [#4392-5006] (Box 29, Cassette 4392-5000)
- Series V: May 2014 Accession, 1991-2002; 2014.103
  Series V: Series V: May 2014 Accession, 1991-2002, Consists of audio in audiocassette and mini-disc format, as well as video in mini-DVs and VHS format, mainly of meetings of the Communist Party of the United States of America. Some of these may be duplicates of items found elsewhere in the collection.
  - National Conference on the Working Class, Chicago (audio cassette tape), Jun 29, 1991 (Box 82)
  - N.C. Meeting (audio cassette tapes), Mar 20, 1993-Mar 21, 1993 (Box 82, Cassette 4-7)
  - N.C. Meeting (audio cassette tapes), Dec 4, 1994-Dec 5, 1994 (Box 82, Cassette 1-2, 6-8)
  - G.) Fund Raising (audio cassette tape), Sep 18, 1993-Sep 19 1993 (Box 82)
  - Jim West - "On Trotskyism" - Board Room (audio cassette tape), Jun 5, 1995 (Box 82)
  - E.) Club Life (audio cassette tape), Sep 18, 1993 -Sep 19, 1993 (Box 82)
  - Building Left Unity (audio cassette tape) (Box 82)
  - Jim West - Labor TUEL (audio cassette tape) (Box 82)
  - William E. Burghardt Du Bois Autobiographical Remarks (audio cassette tape) (Box 82)
  - Winston Party Building - Side 3 (audio cassette tape) (Box 82)
  - YCL 7th Conv Fri Nite (mini [audio] disc) (Box 82)
  - CNPC Opening by Sam Webb (mini [audio] disc), Nov 17, 2002 (Box 82)
  - Interviews of Keren Wheeler, Noel Rabinowitz, and Fred Gaboury (mini [audio] disc), 2002 (Box 82)
  - YCL 7th Conv Sat Day (mini [audio] disc) (Box 82)
  - Unlabeled Mini (Audio) Discs (Box 82, Disk 1-3)
  - BMW Thanksgiving Gig wth Noel, Jason, Larry & Pop, Mark (mini-DV video cassette tape), Nov 1998 (Box 82)
  - Sam Webb Address to NC - Tape 1 (mini-DV video cassette tape), Nov 12, 2002 (Box 82)
  - Sam Webb Address to NC - Tape 2 (mini-DV video cassette tape), Nov 12, 2002 (Box 82)
  - Sid et al Memorial - Tape 1 (mini-DV video cassette tape), Nov 16, 2002 (Box 82)
  - Sid et al Memorial - Tape 2 (mini-DV video cassette tape), Nov 16, 2002 (Box 82)
  - Celebration of the Life of Gus Hall (VHS) (Box 82)
  - Chris Tilton NYU Documentary (VHS) (Box 82)
  - The American and World Communist Movement: A Retrospective Assessment, Comments from a member of the founding generation Sam Darcy (VHS), Jan 29, 1992 (Box 82)
- Series VI: Restricted Materials Relating to Central Review Commission: Addendum, 2014.103; 0.25 1 box (Box 83)